# Mushfiq-ur-Rahman

63/C, Asad Avenue
Mohammadpur, Dhaka-1207
Land Ph: +88-02-9113940
Cell Ph: +88 -0167-3005080
E-mail: mushfiq.rahman057@gmail.com



#### **CAREER SUMMARY:**

I am a marketing professional having experience of more than 10 years in different industries. My area of expertise is Business Development, Brand & Communication, Corporate sales. I worked in some of the renowned organizations like Grameen Phone, SSG, Brother Electronics etc. I am passionate to engage myself in challenging and dynamic job where I have scope to explore, learn and development.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE:**

Working in GIM-Digital Truck (A concern of Galaxy Group) as Key Account Manager, Business Development from January 15, 2020 to till date.

### Job Responsibility-

- 1. Develop trust relationships with a portfolio of major clients to ensure they do not turn to competition
- 2. Acquire a thorough understanding of key customer needs and requirements
- 3. Expand the relationships with existing customers by continuously proposing solutions that meet their objectives
- 4. Ensure the correct products and services are delivered to customers in a timely manner
- 5. Serve as the link of communication between key customers and internal teams
- 6. Resolve any issues and problems faced by customers and deal with complaints to maintain trust
- 7. Play an integral part in generating new sales that will turn into long-lasting relationships
- 8. Prepare regular reports of progress and forecasts to internal and external stakeholders using key account metrics
- Worked in Global Brand Pvt. Ltd. as Deputy Manager, Business Development from July 2018 to February 14, 2020.

#### Job responsibility-

- 1. Responsible for managing several government and private corporate accounts.
- 2. Achieving high sales targets and goals while motivating account executives to do the same.
- 3. Developing and implementing appropriate corporate affairs strategies, programs, and policies for all stakeholders to achieve positive image & brand.
- 4. Managing and ensuring support for different government projects with a proper relationship management.

- 5. Managing and coordinating research into stakeholder's perceptions and image of the corporation, to achieve positive reputation for the corporation.
- 6. Leading, training, and managing other members of the account management team and dealing with any issues that may arise.
- 7. Building new business relationships using existing industry contacts.
- Worked in "Fair Distribution Limited. (FDL)"- National distributor of Samsung as a Relationship Manager, Enterprise Business from December 2016 to June 2018.

# Job responsibility-

- 1. Develop client relationship and achieve sales target through sales channels.
- 2. Plan develop and direct marketing effort for products.
- 3. Create strategies to take advantages of market opportunities.
- 4. Manage external marketing partners such as advertising agencies.
- 5. Assist integration of company's brand guideline.
- 6. Generate sales for a portfolio of accounts and reach the company's sales target.
  - Worked in "Brother International Singapore Pte. Ltd." as Sr. Executive, Corporate Sales from February 2014 to November 2016.

#### Job responsibility-

- 1. Achieving growth and hitting sales targets by successfully managing the sales team
- 2. Designing and implementing a strategic sales plan that expands company's customer base and ensure its strong presence
- 3. Managing recruiting, objectives setting, coaching and performance monitoring of sales representatives.
  - Worked in "Super Star Group (SSG)" as a Senior Executive Brand Management, from July 2011 to January 2014.

# Job responsibility-

- 1. Yearly branding planning, budgeting, implementation, evaluation & presentation of monthly branding activity.
- 2. Provide design and direction for collateral, web, product packaging, and other visual communications media for the company.
- 3. All outdoor advertisement, event planning, implementation, monitoring & billing according to market & corporate requirements.

 Worked in "Grameen Phone Ltd." as an Executive- Outbound Sales from August 2010 to June 2011.

# Job responsibility-

- 1. Proactively aware/inform customers regarding our products/service.
- 2. Close the sale on products and services to new and existing customers. Capture customer insights.
- 3. Maintain targeted KPI on a regular basis.
- 4. Ensure high quality of the sale. In this way enhance Grameen Phone's brand image.
- 5. Show respect towards customers, colleagues and company by a smiling and positive person.

#### **EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION:**

#### **East West University**

Master of Business Administration (MBA) Major in Marketing

#### **East West University**

Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA) Major in Marketing

# **Dhaka City College, Dhaka**

Higher Secondary School Certificate Examination (HSC)

#### Dhanmondi Govt. Boys' High School, Dhaka

Secondary School Certificate Examination (SSC)

#### **COMPUTER LITERACY:**

Operating system : Windows 2000, XP
Office Management: MS Office 2007
Language : Visual Basic, HTML

Design software : Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator

# **LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY:**

Good command in English, Bangla and Hindi language.

IELTS (Academic) score: 6.00

#### **REFERENCE:**

References will be provided upon request.